<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Diversity &amp; Inclusion</title>
    <link>https://www.bridgewater.com/diversity-and-inclusion</link>
    <description>Diversity &amp; Inclusion</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 12:49:48 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.bridgewater.com/diversity-and-inclusion.rss" type="application/rss+xml" rel="self" />
    <item>
      <title>Margo Cook Joins Women’s Influence Network for Fireside Chat</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgewater.com/diversity-and-inclusion/margo-cook-joins-womens-influence-network-for-fireside-chat</link>
      <description>An Independent Director on Bridgewater’s Operating Board of Directors, Margo shared stories of big breaks throughout her career and advice particularly relevant to women working in underrepresented fields.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 12:49:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bridgewater.com/diversity-and-inclusion/margo-cook-joins-womens-influence-network-for-fireside-chat</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sian Beilock Describes the “Spotlight Effect” Within the Workplace</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgewater.com/diversity-and-inclusion/sian-beilock-describes-the-spotlight-effect-within-the-workplace</link>
      <description>President of Barnard College and Independent Director on Bridgewater’s Operating Board of Directors discussed her career and the “spotlight” effect as part of Women’s History Month.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 17:07:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bridgewater.com/diversity-and-inclusion/sian-beilock-describes-the-spotlight-effect-within-the-workplace</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridgewater’s LGBTQ+ Affinity Network Hosts “When We (They) Knew”</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgewater.com/diversity-and-inclusion/bridgewaters-lgbtq-affinity-network-hosts-when-we-they-knew</link>
      <description>During Pride Month, the Bridgewater community gathered to hear Senior Software Engineer Lucas Morales discuss their journey toward authenticity in their gender identity in an event hosted by our LGBTQ+ Affinity Network, BProud.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 15:21:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bridgewater.com/diversity-and-inclusion/bridgewaters-lgbtq-affinity-network-hosts-when-we-they-knew</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sarah Fass: Planning an Inclusive Return to Office</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgewater.com/diversity-and-inclusion/sarah-fass-planning-an-inclusive-return-to-office</link>
      <description>Sarah Fass, Chief Human Resources Officer, engaged in a panel discussion on how offices are evolving as employees prepare to adapt to a post-pandemic world. She explained that Bridgewater’s return to office plan is anchored in being explicitly inclusive of the needs of both individuals and groups.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 13:00:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bridgewater.com/diversity-and-inclusion/sarah-fass-planning-an-inclusive-return-to-office</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kate Manahan: An Honest Look at Benefits</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgewater.com/diversity-and-inclusion/kate-manahan-an-honest-look-at-benefits</link>
      <description>Kate Manahan, Head of Reward and Talent Enablement, recently joined other leaders in a panel discussion on workplace benefits hosted by Luminary NYC, a global professional growth organization for women. During the session, Kate spoke about the importance of companies offering strong benefits not only on paper, but also in how a company’s culture and management empowers employees to take full advantage of benefit offerings.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 12:57:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bridgewater.com/diversity-and-inclusion/kate-manahan-an-honest-look-at-benefits</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
