<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>People</title>
    <link>https://www.bridgewater.com/people</link>
    <description>People</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 15:41:10 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.bridgewater.com/people.rss" type="application/rss+xml" rel="self" />
    <item>
      <title>Natalee Pei &amp; Phil Salinger named as 2022 Council on Foreign Relations Corporate Leaders</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgewater.com/people/natalee-pei-phil-salinger-named-as-2022-council-on-foreign-relations-corporate-leaders</link>
      <description>Natalee and Phil are recognized for their leadership and contributions as members of CFR’s Corporate Leaders Program, a unique professional development opportunity for rising stars.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 15:41:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bridgewater.com/people/natalee-pei-phil-salinger-named-as-2022-council-on-foreign-relations-corporate-leaders</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melissa Saphier &amp; Sean Macrae named as 2019 Council on Foreign Relations Corporate Leaders</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgewater.com/people/melissa-saphier-sean-macrae-named-as-2019-council-on-foreign-relations-corporate-leaders</link>
      <description>Melissa and Sean are recognized for their leadership and contributions as members of CFR’s Corporate Leaders Program, a unique professional development opportunity for rising stars.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 15:37:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bridgewater.com/people/melissa-saphier-sean-macrae-named-as-2019-council-on-foreign-relations-corporate-leaders</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steven Kryger named 2019 Atlantic Council Millennium Fellow</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgewater.com/people/steven-kryger-named-2019-atlantic-council-millennium-fellow</link>
      <description>Steven, a 10-year veteran of the firm, joins a class of 21 fellows who will champion the Council’s mission to build enduring relationships capable of addressing the most pressing global challenges we face.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 15:31:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bridgewater.com/people/steven-kryger-named-2019-atlantic-council-millennium-fellow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Brennan named to 2019 Aspen Institute’s Finance Leaders Fellowship Class</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgewater.com/people/kevin-brennan-named-to-2019-aspen-institutes-finance-leaders-fellowship-class</link>
      <description>Bridgewater’s Co-Head of the Investment Engine and Director of Investment Systems joins a distinguished group of 85 individuals across 19 countries who will focus on building the core values and perspectives necessary for effective leadership in finance and society at-large.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 15:13:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bridgewater.com/people/kevin-brennan-named-to-2019-aspen-institutes-finance-leaders-fellowship-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melody Rollins Named to INvolve’s 2022 EMpower Executive Role Model List</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgewater.com/melody-rollins-named-to-involves-2022-empower-executive-role-model-list</link>
      <description>Supported by Yahoo Finance, the EMpower Role Model Lists recognize leaders who are breaking barriers for people of color within their workplace and beyond.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 16:38:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bridgewater.com/melody-rollins-named-to-involves-2022-empower-executive-role-model-list</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rutendo Chigora Named to EMpower’s 2022 Ethnic Minority Future Leaders list</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgewater.com/people/rutendo-chigora-named-to-empowers-2022-ethnic-minority-future-leaders-list</link>
      <description>For the second year in a row, Investment Associate Rutendo Chigora has been named to the EMpower Ethnic Minority Future Leaders List, recognized for her longstanding commitment to expanding opportunity at Bridgewater and beyond.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 13:19:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bridgewater.com/people/rutendo-chigora-named-to-empowers-2022-ethnic-minority-future-leaders-list</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicole Schmidt Selected for 2022 CSIS Women’s Global Leadership Program</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgewater.com/people/nicole-schmidt-selected-for-2022-csis-womens-global-leadership-program</link>
      <description>Nicole joins a select class of 24 women leaders as part of a one-year fellowship designed to deepen their understanding of critical geopolitical trends in order to thrive in a complex and competitive global environment.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 14:43:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bridgewater.com/people/nicole-schmidt-selected-for-2022-csis-womens-global-leadership-program</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridgewater’s Transition Milestone</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgewater.com/people/bridgewaters-transition-milestone</link>
      <description>Earlier this week, Ray Dalio, Bob Prince, Greg Jensen, and Co-CEOs Nir Bar Dea and Mark Bertolini signed the agreements providing for the transfer of control of Bridgewater from Ray to the Operating Board of Directors, successfully finalizing the terms of this transition.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 17:57:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bridgewater.com/people/bridgewaters-transition-milestone</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atul Narayan named to 2020 the Center for Strategic and International Studies Abshire-Inamori Leadership Cohort</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgewater.com/people/atul-narayan-named-to-2020-the-center-for-strategic-and-international-studies-abshire-inamori-leadership-cohort</link>
      <description>Atul joins a group of leaders from across the US and around the globe, to address the intellectual, ethical, cultural, and policy questions that are central to effective leadership in today’s world.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 18:15:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bridgewater.com/people/atul-narayan-named-to-2020-the-center-for-strategic-and-international-studies-abshire-inamori-leadership-cohort</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
